Aman Narsu

A well-rounded professional that's skilled in SQL, SQLite, Data Analysis, Data Modelling, Machine Learning, and Data Analytics. Qualitative Research. Seeking to leverage my Technical Support experience and analytical skills, to start a new a career as a Data Scientist.

CONTACT

Bo'ness- UK

+447788612857| narsuaman@gmail.com LinkedIn: <u>www.linkedin.com/in/aman-</u>

narsu-2258141a6/

Github: https://github.com/amannarsu/

Hyperion:

<u>www.hyperiondev.com/portfolio/AN2402</u> <u>0013196/</u>

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Python and SQL programming
- Github
- Microsoft Office
- Object-Oriented-Programming
- Numpy, Pandas
- Postman and APIs
- Data Analysis
- Data visualisation
- Data transformation and manipulation
- Natural Language Processing (NLP)
- Source version control
- Azure Administration

SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptive Communicator
- Ability to Work Under Pressure.
- Excel at Decision Making.
- Time Management.
- Self-motivated.
- Multi-Tasking.
- · Conflict Resolution.
- Team worker.
- Team Training

EDUCATION

Data Science Bootcamp HyperionDev

March 2024 - June 2024

B.Sc. In Networking at Anglia Ruskin University

September 2009- June 2013

REFERENCES

References available on request

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Analytical and problem solver who excels in resolving complex problems with more than 6 Years of Experience in the IT field.

Calm in stressful situation and good People Skills with ability to Adapt to any stuation. Great problem solver and team worker.

While working I am also following my passion for data science and am building up my experties in the field by actively taking part in the indept bootcamp for Data Science by HyperionDev.

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

Data Science Bootcamp | HyperionDev

03/2024 - ongoing

The Data Science bootcamp covers Python, probability, statistics, data science libraries and fundamental machine learning concepts.

- Achieved an overall grade average of 100% for the bootcamp tasks.
- Implemented end-to-end features using Python for capstone projects.
- Demonstrated proficiency in version control using Git for my capstone projects.
- Successfully completed practical, real-world projects.
- Participated in debugging sessions, honing problem-solving skills in a collaborative environment.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Technical Support Analyst (Current)| Atto

-Jul 2020 - current

- Onboarding customers while support the Customer success team while managing customer requirements.
- Speaking with KEY business partners using Teams or emails and something using Video conferences.
- Assist and help manage customer during major incidents and raising awareness in the relevant channels.
- Working with the Dev team to solve issues, by testing and investigations.
- Tracking and raising issues with data suppliers.
- Updating existing documents and creating up to date compliance docs
- Proactively managing issue internally with our data providers and monitoring internal issues

ITOM Support Engineer | IFS Assyst

-May 2019 - Jul 2020

- Providing technical support for ITAM Software to debug, test and provide effective solution to the customer.
- Collaborating with 3rd party and Management
- Handle escalations and deal with high priority issues daily.
- Working on fixed Shifts, but adjusting shifts based on client's requirements and needs.
- Creating Customer facing documentation and dealing with their basic and Advanced Queries.
- Independent working and guiding team where required.

Complaints Manager | TCS

- -June 2018 to May 2019
- Handling customers issues from start to finish, Managing L1 teams for prompt resolution.
- Looking after customer compensation.
- Escalating to internal teams and 3rd party teams
- Liaising with the sales team to get the correct order for the customer.

Technical Support | SYKES GLOBAL SERVICES

- -Oct 2016 to May 2018
- Servicing customer routers and Wi-Fi device using verbal communication, Citrix and iPhone.
- Making sure there is no electronic interference or problems with the network related to Wi-Fi, Ip addresses, gateway address and incorrect connectivity on hardware.
- In-dept troubleshooting on hardware to reach the root of the issue and promoting the company products to assist with this.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Practical experience in database management and working with SQL, MSSQL Server and Azure Data Studio in live environment.
- Experience with Git for version control, to manage educational portfolio and data.
- Pursuing additional training for Python on Udemy to solidify my foundational skills.